

CONTACT

9

Rivadavia, Mendoza, Argentina.



lagos.herrera.luca@gmail .com



<u>luca-lagos.github.io</u>



<u>github.com/luca-lagos</u>



codepen.io/luca-lagos



linkedin.com/in/lucalagos/

HARD SKILLS

Frontend development with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap y JQuery.

Backend development with Java -Spring y NodeJs - Express.

Databases SQL y NoSQL with MySQL y MongoDB.

Agile methodologies with SCRUM.

SOFT SKILLS

Good team communication.

Motivation in the resolution of problems.

Serenity in the face of difficulties.

Flexibility and camaraderie.

Respectful and empathetic.

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native).

Basic english.

LUCA LAGOS

Software developer

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer dedicated to the design and construction of web applications, and with experience and knowledge in both the frontend and backend roles. I've been passionate about technology since I was a teenager, an amateur in sports, drawing and film, and a video game addict.

EXPERIENCE

Full-stack developer

<u>Dirección General de Escuelas - Government of Mendoza</u> | September 2021 - November 2021

• Development, maintenance and updating of applications that integrate the digital ecosystem of the public and private education system of Mendoza, Argentina.

University professor

9-006 "Francisco Humberto Tolosa" | May 2021 - Present

• Teaching in subjects of Informatics I and II of the Higher Technician in Business Administration.

Network admin

4-259 | May 2021 - Present

- Maintenance of school networks.
- Maintenance of technological equipment.

Network admin

4-094 "Félix Pesce Scarso" | May 2019 - Present

- Maintenance of school networks.
- Active participation in school projects as a teacher.
- Conducting training.

EDUCATION

Software developer

PT-026 "San Vicente de Paul" | April 2019 - August 2021

- Implementation of required system analysis methods.
- Software development.

Computer and Network Technician

IES 9-021 | April 2016 - December 2018

- Installation, configuration and maintenance of computer equipment.
- Implementation of methods and protocols for installing network systems.